<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Artwork Beef</title>
    <link>https://rmrector.github.io/script.artwork.beef/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Artwork Beef</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 22:44:39 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://rmrector.github.io/script.artwork.beef/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>First usage</title>
      <link>https://rmrector.github.io/script.artwork.beef/usage/firstusage/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2017 22:45:06 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rmrector.github.io/script.artwork.beef/usage/firstusage/</guid>
      <description>Artwork Beef must process all items in your library, and will do so automatically. There are some artwork in the file system that isn&amp;rsquo;t added to Kodi&amp;rsquo;s database with any/many other tools. It will also check web services for new artwork to fill out any media items still missing some, unless &amp;ldquo;Do not automatically add artwork from web services, only identify local files&amp;rdquo; is enabled. If you haven&amp;rsquo;t been managing movie collection artwork, Kodi sets posters and fanart to those of one of the movies in the collection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fun without add-ons</title>
      <link>https://rmrector.github.io/script.artwork.beef/skins/addonfreefun/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 22:44:56 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rmrector.github.io/script.artwork.beef/skins/addonfreefun/</guid>
      <description>Because who wants another dependency?
Display multiple fanart Artwork Helper isn&amp;rsquo;t strictly needed, how about that? It is a bit more work though.
The trick is to use a fadelabel control to gather multiple InfoLabels and randomize them, then use that control&amp;rsquo;s label as the final image to be displayed.
&amp;lt;control type=&amp;quot;fadelabel&amp;quot; id=&amp;quot;398045&amp;quot;&amp;gt; &amp;lt;description&amp;gt;Randomizer for plugin-free multiple fanart&amp;lt;/description&amp;gt; &amp;lt;top&amp;gt;-1000&amp;lt;/top&amp;gt; &amp;lt;!-- Don&#39;t need to see it, but can&#39;t change its visibility.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Artwork helper</title>
      <link>https://rmrector.github.io/script.artwork.beef/skins/artworkhelper/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 22:45:47 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rmrector.github.io/script.artwork.beef/skins/artworkhelper/</guid>
      <description>Artwork Helper provides skins with a few options for building a list of images for a multiimage or list control from images available via InfoLabels. This is a small add-on that skins can use as a dependency, only doing what a skin asks it to do.
Current version only works for Kodi 17 and 18, use version 0.7.1 for 15 and 16.
Add-on setting There is an add-on setting to pull extrafanart and extrathumbs from the filesystem, if there is only a single image in the library.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Image files</title>
      <link>https://rmrector.github.io/script.artwork.beef/usage/fromfiles/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2017 22:45:58 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rmrector.github.io/script.artwork.beef/usage/fromfiles/</guid>
      <description>Downloading and managing local artwork files By default, Artwork Beef does not modify existing local artwork files. There are some options to change that, though. With the settings &amp;ldquo;Download these artwork types to the local file system&amp;rdquo; you can configure exactly which types of artwork to download for each media type. By default most video library images will be saved next to the media files with the most specific file names detailed below, with options to save movie and music video artwork without the base file name if you like, and options to save movie and music video fanart# to an &amp;ldquo;extrafanart&amp;rdquo; directory for skins using the classic style.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Add-on settings &amp; actions</title>
      <link>https://rmrector.github.io/script.artwork.beef/usage/settings/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 15:50:04 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rmrector.github.io/script.artwork.beef/usage/settings/</guid>
      <description>Artwork Beef configuration and manual actions when run from &amp;ldquo;Program Add-ons&amp;rdquo;.
General &amp;ldquo;Add artwork for new videos / music after library updates&amp;rdquo; The main process of Artwork Beef. Runs after library updates to add extended artwork for media items newly added to the Kodi library, either from the file system or web services. Video and music are configured separately. A media item is only &amp;ldquo;new&amp;rdquo; once, after it has been scanned it is no longer &amp;ldquo;new&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advanced control</title>
      <link>https://rmrector.github.io/script.artwork.beef/usage/commands/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2018 14:50:55 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rmrector.github.io/script.artwork.beef/usage/commands/</guid>
      <description>Scripts, skins, and other add-ons can use commands to control bits and pieces of Artwork Beef.
Run automatic processing on the library You can disable the automatic processing after library updates and schedule them with something like the Kodi Callbacks add-on or cron, or trigger them in some other way.
 Process new items  NotifyAll(script.artwork.beef:control, ProcessNewVideos) NotifyAll(script.artwork.beef:control, ProcessNewMusic)  Process new and old items, but not all in between  NotifyAll(script.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why replace extrafanart/extrathumbs</title>
      <link>https://rmrector.github.io/script.artwork.beef/skins/whyreplaceextra/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 22:46:53 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rmrector.github.io/script.artwork.beef/skins/whyreplaceextra/</guid>
      <description>I think that multiple fanart for individual media items should be integrated into the library like all other artwork. Here is a list of my reasons.
 Media file organization and skin display should be completely independent. Skins and other interfaces should access all library artwork in the same way.  or a list of particulars:
 Kodi&amp;rsquo;s support for freely named artwork in the library is pretty great, so let&amp;rsquo;s use it!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>