<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Artwork Beef</title>
    <link>https://rmrector.github.io/script.artwork.beef/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Artwork Beef</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 22:44:39 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://rmrector.github.io/script.artwork.beef/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>First usage</title>
      <link>https://rmrector.github.io/script.artwork.beef/usage/firstusage/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2017 22:45:06 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rmrector.github.io/script.artwork.beef/usage/firstusage/</guid>
      <description>The first time Artwork Beef runs it will process all items in your library. There are some artwork in the file system that isn&amp;rsquo;t added to Kodi&amp;rsquo;s database with any/many other tools. It will also check web services for new artwork to fill out any media items still missing some, unless &amp;ldquo;Automatically add artwork from file system only&amp;rdquo; is enabled. If you haven&amp;rsquo;t been managing movie collection artwork, Kodi sets posters and fanart to those of one of the movies in the collection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NFO and image files</title>
      <link>https://rmrector.github.io/script.artwork.beef/usage/fromfiles/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2017 22:45:58 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rmrector.github.io/script.artwork.beef/usage/fromfiles/</guid>
      <description>Artwork file naming conventions for the video library Artwork Beef will pick up any properly named artwork files next to your video files. It has two conventions for loading most artwork: [media file name]-[art type].[ext] for movies, episodes, and music videos, and [art type].[ext] for TV shows and as a less specific alternative for movies and music videos with their own directories. This generally matches Kodi&amp;rsquo;s file naming conventions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fun without add-ons</title>
      <link>https://rmrector.github.io/script.artwork.beef/skins/addonfreefun/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 22:44:56 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rmrector.github.io/script.artwork.beef/skins/addonfreefun/</guid>
      <description>Because who wants another dependency?
Display multiple fanart Artwork Helper isn&amp;rsquo;t strictly needed, how about that? It is a bit more work though.
The trick is to use a fadelabel control to gather multiple InfoLabels and randomize them, then use that control&amp;rsquo;s label as the final image to be displayed.
&amp;lt;control type=&amp;quot;fadelabel&amp;quot; id=&amp;quot;398045&amp;quot;&amp;gt; &amp;lt;description&amp;gt;Randomizer for plugin-free multiple fanart&amp;lt;/description&amp;gt; &amp;lt;top&amp;gt;-1000&amp;lt;/top&amp;gt; &amp;lt;!-- Don&#39;t need to see it, but can&#39;t change its visibility.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Artwork helper</title>
      <link>https://rmrector.github.io/script.artwork.beef/skins/artworkhelper/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 22:45:47 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rmrector.github.io/script.artwork.beef/skins/artworkhelper/</guid>
      <description>Artwork Helper provides skins with a few options for building a list of images for a multiimage or list control from images available via InfoLabels. This is a small add-on that skins can use as a dependency, only doing what a skin asks it to do.
Current version only works for Kodi 17 and 18, use version 0.7.1 for 15 and 16.
Add-on setting There is an add-on setting to pull extrafanart and extrathumbs from the filesystem, if there is only a single image in the library.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why replace extrafanart/extrathumbs</title>
      <link>https://rmrector.github.io/script.artwork.beef/skins/whyreplaceextra/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2017 22:46:53 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rmrector.github.io/script.artwork.beef/skins/whyreplaceextra/</guid>
      <description>Kodi&amp;rsquo;s support for freely named artwork in the library is pretty great, so let&amp;rsquo;s use it! Avoid filesystem delays/access issues (unavailable network file system, removable media) when the images have been cached. Classic extrafanart always had to hit the file system at least once when the path changed to get a list of all extrafanart, even if they were all cached. Skins can more easily work with all fanart together (main + extra fanart)  There are plugin:// paths to stitch together fanart images for &amp;lsquo;multiimage&amp;rsquo; controls, &amp;lsquo;fanart&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;fanart#&amp;rsquo; alike!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>